要是我能把四个帮派的头目
What would you say if I can get you the leaders
都给你弄来呢
to all four gangs?
那我要帮你做什么
What's it gonna cost me?
《金斯敦市长》前情提要
他们要把我们关多久
How long they planning on holding us?
你们要多久才能调教好里面的帮派
How long's it gonna take you to get your house together inside?
趴在地上 赶紧的
Down on the ground, now.
你们不知道我孙子是谁吗
You don't know who my grandson is.
这是我们来的原因
That's why we're here.
不该发生这事的
That was not supposed to happen.
这笔帐迟早要还
There's gon' be some payback.
我要以牙还牙搞你们的家人
This shit's gonna hit close to home.
赶紧他妈的给我放出去
Get me the fuck outta here.
巡逻队追了他几条街
Patrol caught him a few blocks up.
我想和他谈谈
I wanna talk to him.
哦 天哪 这是怎么了
Oh my God, what happened?
他反抗了
He resisted.
这是你的新家
This is your new home.
希望没了 人也死了
Hope dies, we die.
来聊聊我想让你帮的忙吧
Let's talk about my favor.
你想让我转移什么东西
What am I moving?
去找金属制品吧
Look for metal.
只要你能找到 你就是救世主
If you find it, you are the savior.
如果是他们找到
If they find it...
你就自求多福吧
God help you.
敬请期待
金斯敦商业 住宅区超级空间
那边还好吗
Everything okay over there?!
好 没事
Yeah! Yeah, all good!
我还以为挖到了一个旧污水管之类呢
Just thought I hit a fuckin' old sewage line or somethin'!
只是垃圾
It's just trash!
马特西克
商业地产开发
NEW字幕组翻译
翻译  鹅蔼玲
翻译  炭炭
翻译  千阳
翻译  Melody
翻译  江湖
翻译  头上长仙草
校对  头上长仙草
校对  千阳
时间轴  长颂
时间轴  斤日
时间轴  隔壁老宋
啦啦队  千阳
总监  千阳
CSEG克隆字幕提取组
提取  Caliro
@CSEG克隆字幕提取组
B区囚犯 编号991913
Inmate Brown. 991913.
到检查站报到
Report to the checkpoint.
不用
No. Uh-uh, uh-uh.
我到时给你留个铺位 兄弟
I'll save you a bunk, man.
不用 兄弟 这怎么回事
No, man. What the fuck?
听着
Aight, look.
有我呢
I got you.
-明白吗  -我知道
- Know that. - Yeah, I hear you.
你兄弟打算把这事糊弄过去 老兄
Your boy's lettin' this shit slip, bruh.
看来你和我
Looks like me and you 'bout to
得亲自让这个狗日的搞清楚情况
have to make this motherfucker right on our own.
我给你列份名单
I'll line some shit out for you.
让他们准备
Make sure they ready for
迎接天王老子的愤怒吧
the motherfuckin' king up in there.
小心后背 老兄
Watch your six, bruh.
好
Yeah.
不不不 你别想就这么甩掉我
Nah, nah, nah, nah, you not about to shake me off,
不得擅闯监狱 违者重罪处理
你这个玉米杆一样的混蛋
you corn stock lookin'-ass motherfucker.
什么 什么
What, what?
你说话给我放尊重点
Get that bass out your fuckin' voice!
小自[黑人对白人的谑称]
Opie.
听着
Now...
我看到有人走了
I see shit movin'.
我要知道是谁 去哪
I get to know the who, the where,
到底在搞什么鬼
and what the fuck.
我在工作呢 邦尼一边儿去
I'm workin' here, Bunny. Hop along.
他妈的要转移人吗
Motherfuckers gettin' transferred?
-有人要走  -谁
- Someone is. - Who?
我他妈怎么知道
The fuck should I know?
你应该高兴才对
You should be feeling peachy.
你会有新床
You get a new fucking bed.
有吃的 不用在这里热到融化
Some food, get out of this blistering heat.
-去哪  -重要吗
- Where? - It matter?
城里有五所监狱
There are five fuckin' houses in this town.
开车不到六小时又有三个
Another three within six hours.
他们像施肥一样把你们散开 看看能结出什么好果子
They'll spread you out like manure and see what grows.
-操你妈  -你想待在这儿吗
- Fuck you. - You wanna stay here?
我做了交易 混蛋 懂吗
I got a deal, motherfucker. Aight?
手机给我
Gimme your phone.
想的美
Fuck you!
把你手机给我 兄弟 我打给麦克
Give your fuckin' phone man, I'm gotta call Mike.
别忘了你他妈是谁
Don't forget who the fuck you are.
因为到了晚上
Because at the end of the day,
我回家 开罐冰镇啤酒 躺进暖和的被窝
I go home, I crack a cold beer, I get in my warm bed,
跟我的辣妞睡觉
I get some hot pussy.
你只能待在你现在站的地方 勒布朗[黑人球星]
And you stay right where the fuck you are, LeBron.
听着
You know...
麦克会知道的 懂吧
Mike gon' find out about this shit, aight?
等他知道了 我就明明白白告诉他
And when he do, I'mma be crystal fucking clear
谁帮了兄弟
who was hookin' a brother up,
谁对这计划袖手旁观
and who was gettin' away with the goddamn plan.
你懂吗
You feel me?
要是麦克知道你给这事添堵
You better prepare to drop to them boney-ass knees of yours
你就准备好双膝跪地
for some dick suckin' if Mike find out
给人嗦鸡巴吧
you got in the way of this world gettin' right.
手机
Phone!
又怎么了
What? Yeah?
卡尼
Carney?
他们要把人运走 麦克
They movin' people, Mike.
这事你知道吗 王八蛋
You know about this, motherfucker?
-邦尼  -麦克 应该是你干这事
- Bunny! - Mike, you supposed to
他的手机怎么在你手里
- be on this shit! - How'd you get his phone?
应该是你开着那辆破车进来
You supposed to be the driver of the fuckin' wagon,
而不是被人当枪使 麦克
not the goddamn horse, Mike!
好好好 我来处理
Yeah, look. I'll get into it.
听着 这车的名单里
Look, my motherfuckin' name
最好别有我的名字
better not be get called in this bitch.
我的天 邦尼 你放松一点好不好
Jesus, Bunny, will you relax for God's sakes?
邦尼 他们不会叫你的名字的
Look Bunny, they're not gonna call your name!
好吗
Okay?
转移囚犯很正常
I mean, they move inmates all the time.
大概是处理打架之类的蠢事
It's probably a reaction to a fight, something stupid.
就是表个态
They're makin' a statement.
你看到哪个老大被运走了吗
Alright? You seen any of the main players marchin' out?
-没有 还没有  -就是嘛
- No, not yet. - Exactly.
美国政府中心 这里代指市政府
是国会山的混蛋搞的鬼
It's some asshole in Capitol Hill!
好吗 他只是耍威风
All right? He's just swingin' a dick.
我来搞定 明白吗
I'll take care of it! You hear me?
现在 麦克 现在就去处理
Now, Mike. Deal with this shit now.
因为我不喜欢这种感觉
'Cause I don't like this feelin'.
我应该被转移到的地方
The only place I'm supposed to be gettin' transferred to
只能是我的床 麦克
is my fuckin' bed, Mike.
听明白了吗
You hear that?
我明白 不用担心 好吗
I got it! Don't worry, all right?
操 这大清早的
Fuck. This is my morning.
早上好啊 又是操蛋的一天
Good fucking morning to me.
混蛋
Motherfucker.
嘿 麦克 有时间吗
Hey, Mike. You got a second?
-有  -抱歉 麦克
- Yeah. - Sorry, Mike.
不 你不可以跟任何人交谈 明白了吗
No, you're not talkin' to anybody, you understand me?
你每多说一句话
Every time you open your mouth,
都会多判你一年
you add another year to your sentence.
-见伊芙琳了吗  -在她办公室
- You seen Evelyn? - In her office.
她正焦头烂额呢
She's elbow deep in it.
暴乱之后 他们就准备拿这件事开刀了
They're sharpening their knives after that riot.
经过23号那场屠杀
The massacre on 23rd?
场面就更很难看了
Not a good look for the home team.
他们开了地方检察官 我估计下一任也不好过
They bounce the DA, I don't think they're playin' next man up.
好 谢了
Yeah. Okay, thanks.
-麦克  -怎么了
- Hey, Mike. - Yeah?
这家伙要进去了 你在锚湾那儿有人吗
This guy goes in, you got any swing at Anchor Bay?
行 到时候跟我说一下他去哪儿
Yeah, let me know where he lands,
我看情况来办
I'll see what I can do.
-明白  -谢了 麦克
- You got it. - Thanks, Mike!
-好  -我怎么跟你说的
- Yeah. - What did I say to you?
-她在里面吗  -在
- She inside? - Yes.
所以...
So...
你听说这场闹剧了吗
Did you know about this shit show?
你脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
清理帐篷城
Clearin' out Tent City.
行吧
Yeah.
麦克 你觉得这件事还得需要多长时间
Mike, how long did you think that this was gonna keep goin'?
我不知道啊 伊芙琳
Well, I don't know, Evelyn!
可能需要我们把整套流程都走一遍
Maybe long enough for us to finish what we started.
是吗
Right?
我是说 如果这些领头的没法来领导
I mean, why put the fuckin' leaders inside
为什么还要把他们关在监狱里
if they have no chance to lead?
我根本控制不了惩戒所的行动
I don't have control over the moves the DOC makes!
还有你们那帮人的所作所为
Or the moves that you and your associates make.
说实话 麦克 我自己有太多烂摊子要收拾
Honestly, Mike, I have so much shit on my plate right now,
我已经没心思管这多余的事了
I do not have room for gravy.
多余的事
Gravy?
你做了交易 伊芙琳
You made deals, Evelyn.
用我的名字担保 亲口承诺的交易
Deals with my name in your fuckin' mouth.
我说了 目前还有更大的问题
Like I said. Bigger problems.
监狱里死了那么多人
The ACLU is lookin' for someone to take the fall
美国公民自由联盟还在找人背这个黑锅
for the deaths in the prison.
司法部那边我压力很大
I have DOJ fuckin' pressure.
他们想把所有人一网打尽
They're lookin' to burn this whole fuckin' house down.
包括我
Including me.
可能还会牵涉到你特警队的朋友
And this house might fall on your SWAT friend, too,
所以请原谅我 我根本不关心
so forgive me if I don't give a shit
几个街头黑帮头目有什么不便的地方
if a couple of street criminals are inconvenienced.
我们跟邦尼·华盛顿 还有其他帮派头目
We made a deal with Bunny Washington
都达成了交易
and the other generals.
你明白吗
Do you understand that?
地方检察官在准备释放文件 但这...
The DA is working on release papers, but this is...
很复杂
complicated.
对我们来说都是
For all of us.
就算他签了
And once he signs,
法官仍然还是要签字
the judge still has to sign off, too.
你就他妈糊弄我吧 伊芙琳
You're so full of shit, Evelyn!
你他妈还是走吧 麦克
You know what? Just fuckin' leave, Mike.
我他妈根本没有时间管这摊子烂事
I don't have the time or the fuckin' bandwidth for this.
这家伙他妈的用我给他的资源
This guy's fucking using the bus that I fucking gave him
给自己谋利
for his own fuckin' benefit!
真把自己当大爷一样
To make him look like less of a limp dick
就他妈是个怂逼
than he already fuckin' is.
他会搞砸这一切的 伊芙琳
He's gonna fuck it up, Evelyn!
死伤不停 混战不止
More bodies. More fuckin' chaos.
你想看到这些吗
You want that?
他妈的混蛋
Fuckin' prick.
他不了解这些人...
He doesn't know these people...
但我知道...
I do...
如果里面一发不可收拾了
And when shit goes south on the inside,
他在外面跑不掉的
it's gonna find him on the outside.
你刚刚是在威胁地方检察官吗 麦克
Did you just fucking threaten the District Attorney, Mike?
就只是让他签个字 行吗
Just get him to sign the fuckin' papers, would ya?!
伊芙琳 我需要我的人放出来
Evelyn, I need my guy the fuck out.
我现在没了工作
I don't really have a job right now.
虽然麦克说...
Although Mike, he says...
他需要我的帮助 我也能出一份力
he needs my help, I can help out,
一些乱七八糟的事 但...
some shit like that, but...
我不清楚
I don't know.
我有了个孩子
Havin' a kid.
给他取了你的名字
Namin' him after you.
米契·麦克拉斯基
亲爱的儿子 哥哥
我只是不...
I just don't...
我不知道应该怎么做 米契
I don't know what to do, Mitch.
我觉得我真的搞砸了
I, I feel like I'm really fuckin' this up.
我只是需要一些帮助 老哥
You know, I just need some fuckin' help, man.
我只是...
I just...
如果你能帮我一把
If you could fuckin' help me out,
我真的感激涕零
I'd really appreciate it.
操
Fuck.
五分钟后回来
我又不是管事的 麦克
I don't control shit in here, Mike, you know?
我是说 我只能告诉你哪些人
I mean, I can tell you when somebody gets
在什么时候会被转移
transferred or moved,
但除了这个 我也束手无策
but other than that, my hands are tied right now.
好好 明白
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it.
那就帮我盯好 好吧
Just be my eyes and ears, all right?
盯好他们的一举一动
If anything moves out there.
-包在我身上  -好 谢谢
- No shit. - Okay? Thank you.
早上好 怎么了
Good morning. What's up?
就是...
Oh, just...
总是感觉怪怪的
It's fuckin' weird bein' here.
这个地方...
This...
感觉跟之前的很像
place looks just like the old one.
是啊
Yeah.
来点儿吗
You want some?
好啊 谢了
Yeah, please.
丽贝卡跑哪里去了
Where the fuck's Rebecca?
她留了张便利贴 上面写着"五分钟后回来"
She's a Post-It note. "Back in five" it said.
怎么了 弟
What's up, Brother?
天哪
Oh, Jesus.
我需要工作 麦克 不是杂务
I need a job, Mike. Not a chore.
一份正正经经的工作
Like a fuckin' job, job.
我能帮上忙的
And I can help, man.
我有两把刷子
I'm good at shit.
你知道吗 我能...
You know? I can...
我是个工作狂
I'm a fuckin' worker, man.
你知道的
You know that.
嗯 所以我让你去查火车和公交
Yeah, that's why I sent you to the train station, the buses,
去找到艾丽丝
to find Iris, you know?
我去了
And I did that.
但是我不可能每天去那
But I can't keep posting up, just...
只守株待兔啊 麦克
waitin' for her to appear, Mike.
我能干这里的活
I can do shit here.
我能帮你腾出时间
I, I can free up time for you.
你的活都堆满了 麦克
Because you've got a full house, Mike.
自从监狱暴乱之后就是如此
Been that way ever since the riot.
你需要搭把手啊 哥
You need hands, Brother.
我有两只啊
I got idle ones.
我想要出份力 麦克
I need to contribute, Mike.
你懂的 男人必须...
You know, a man's gotta...
必须感觉自己有价值
you know, feel like he's worth somethin'.
你懂吧
You know?
好了 是这样的
Okay, here's the deal...
这东西和钱一样
This stuff is as good as money.
严格来说 它们并不存在
Technically, they don't exist
因为它们被用于各种犯罪活动
because they were used with a bunch of criminal stuff.
但是 很重要的但是
But, and this is a big but...
严格来说
Technically...
尽管现在已经不再发行了
Though they aren't issuing them anymore,
但是如果发行者还在
if the issuer is still active,
这些债券就可以兑换现金
the value of the bonds can be recovered.
所以 就算我们只兑换十分之一
So, even if we get back a tenth of what they're worth,
都算百万富翁了
we're still fuckin' millionaires.
囚犯转运
M区囚犯617178
Inmate Mann. 617178.
到检查站报到
Report to exit checkpoint.
能聊两句吗
I get a word?
说
Speak.
就我跟你
Me and you.
这事全他妈搞砸了 你知道我的意思吗
This is some fucked-up shit, you know what I'm sayin'?
嗯
Uh-huh.
你兄弟坑了我们
Your boy screwed us.
把这事处理好了 他才是我兄弟
He ain't my boy 'til he make this shit right.
麦克应该知道这事的走向
Mike's supposed to know how this shit goes,
应该是我们中的一员
supposed to be one of us.
什么意思
What the hell that mean?
你觉得他耍了我们
You think he played us.
-他不是那种人  -你确定吗
- He ain't like that. - You sure?
我没看到那个王八蛋在里面摇笼子
I don't see that motherfucker rattlin' no cages.
我只看到他在外面
All I see is him outside,
你被困在这个笼子里 等着被转移
and you stuck in this cage waitin' to be shipped out
就像等着被运到屠宰场的牛一样
like some fucking cattle to the slaughterhouse.
你最好小心点
You best be careful,
你嘴里说的那个名字 卡斯帕
you got that damn name in your mouth, Casper.
我只是说
I'm just sayin'.
如果我们不快点出去
We don't get outta here soon,
就不知道什么时候能出去了
don't know when we'll ever get out.
要我看
Way I see it,
你已经在里面揍了人
you did some assault and shit in here already.
把我们害惨了
You fucked a brother up good.
要是有人盯上了
Wrong dude gets eyes on that,
你还没开始 又得蹲十年
you're lookin' at another ten before you even start.
让你的兄弟去做他该做的
Tell your boy to do his fuckin' job.
你翻我的保险箱了
You been in my lockbox?
你不会想在这里找麻烦的 小美女
You do not want none of this smoke, Shortcake.
我没在开玩笑
I ain't fuckin' around!
那里面有钱 有药
I had cash, and I had pills.
行啊 你想找麻烦是吧
Okay, so you wanna do this?
我只想知道我的东西在哪
I just wanna know where my shit is.
你是新来的
You're new.
所以我不会弄花你的脸
So I'mma save that pretty face.
你的钱大概在楼上
The cash you had is probably upstairs.
还有你袋子里的那些药丸
And those pills you keep in that little baggie?
大概是被你自己吃了
Probably just went in your mouth.
懂吗
Okay?
走了 姐妹
Let's go, ladies!
我们还要挣钱呢
We got money to make!
贱人
Fuckin' bitch.
母鬣狗负责捕猎
The matriarch hyena does the hunting.
她们和大部分动物不一样
They're not like most animals.
她们团结一致 阻止内斗
They band together to stop fights.
处理团体的内部问题
And deal with the problems inside the clan.
你...
Are you...
会成为我们的问题吗 艾丽丝
going to be a problem in our clan, Iris?
给我十分钟
Give me ten.
有新消息吗
Got news for me?
那个该死的检察官 那个白痴
This fuckin' DA. This prick.
他拿着这事四处招摇欢呼
He's takin' a victory lap for this bust.
让他咿瑟一会
Give him a minute,
就会签署那该死的文件
then he's gonna sign the fuckin' papers,
他会让法官盖章的
he's gonna get the judge to stamp it,
然后你们就会出来了 好吗
and then you're out in the free world, okay?
我们就搞定了
Then we're done here.
麦克 他们每天都在转运人
They're shippin' people out every day, Mike.
要不了一周
A week from now,
这个地方就没人了
they gonna be tearin' this whole place down.
我知道
I know.
听着 麦克 我他妈不想再趟这趟浑水了
Look man, I ain't fuckin' with gettin' back on this ride, Mike.
这应该只是个临时协议
This was supposed to be a temporary deal.
是临时的
It is.
但我感觉不是 麦克
It ain't feelin' like it, Mike.
我不是来这个什么狗屁锚湾铁笼里
I ain't here for settin' up the game all over again,
洗心革面的 麦克
in some Anchor Bay bullshit-style pen, Mike!
我不是 我重整了这里的秩序
I'm not! I set the order here!
我完成我的工作了 现在轮到你了 兄弟
I did my shit. It's your fuckin' turn, man!
是的 你做到了
Yes, you did.
我会搞定我该做的 好吗
And I'm getting my side done, okay?
放松
Just relax.
我他妈都在泥坑里撒尿了 兄弟
I'm pissin' in a fuckin' trough, man.
我都成了这狗地方的泥城之王了
I'm the king of Mudville up in this bitch.
你现在竟然叫我冷静
Now you, you tellin' me to be cool and shit?
等你把外面的事料理好的时候
Wait for you to get the order goin' on the outside,
我不知道会被运到什么鬼地方
while I get shipped over to who the fuck knows where?
我会把你弄出来的
I'm gonna get you the fuck outta here.
好吗 我向你保证
Okay? You have my word.
就...
Just...
让拉斐尔来掌事 行吗 让他来
Put Rafael on point, right? Set him up, and...
不 他不能在我的阴影下掌事 懂吗
No, man, he can't run shit in my shadow, all right?
只要我在这 就是我掌事
As long as I'm here, I'm point.
你懂这规矩
You know how this work.
我需要你继续相信我
I need you to continue trusting me.
哥们 现在看起来
Man, it's startin' to feel like
相信你会倒霉 麦克
trusting you is bad for business, Mike.
这里有很多人
You got motherfuckers in this bitch
不待见你
lookin' at you sideways.
我也不怪他们
And I can't blame 'em.
你要是不快点把事办好
You don't get this shit right right fuckin' fast,
我可无法阻止
I cannot stop shit from doin'
接下来要出什么乱子 亲
what the fuck it's gonna do, baby.
大家就该自作主张了
People gon' take their own.
现在有些气急败坏的人
And right now, you got some...
正盯着你呢
angry-ass motherfuckers lookin' right at you.
谁
Who?
很难说谁会先出头
It's hard to say who's gonna come knockin'.
我能应付得了
I'll handle it.
哥们 你比米契更能抗子弹吗
Man, you ain't bulletproof any more than Mitch was, man.
他那个只是偶然事件
And that shit was some random-ass shit.
现在这事可没那么简单
This shit right here, it's not gon' be that.
这笔帐迟早要还
This shit gon' be some payback.
多谢你提醒我
Thanks for the warning.
你进入倒计时了 麦克
You on the clock now, Mike.
每一秒钟 每一分钟
Every second. Every minute.
咱们都在被倒计时 邦尼
We're all on the clock, Bunny.
从出生那天开始就是
Since the day we're fuckin' born.
好吗 都是跟老天借来的时间
Okay? This is all just borrowed time.
麦克 把你的事都料理好 不然他们会来找你麻烦
Mike, get your shit in order, or they comin' for your ass.
并且不久后
And soon.
就无力回天了
Reachin' a point of no return.
在车里等我
Wait in the car.
咱们要迟到了 爸爸
We gonna be late, Dad.
马上就好
Just be a minute.
你咋又来找我
Makin' this a habit.
我着急找你谈谈
Yeah, I needed to get you first thing.
那就打电话啊
Well, use the phone.
-我要送孩子上学  -我是想打电话的
- I'm takin' my kid to school. - Well, I would.
你先听我说 我知道 我懂
Just give me a minute, though. I know, I get it.
你有没有...
Do you...
你收到转监的通知了吗
Did you get heads up on these fuckin' transfers?
收到了
I get a heads up, yeah.
你咋没告诉我一声呢
You didn't wanna share that?
你告诉我监狱群架的事了吗
Like you shared that smackdown?
我是想保护你
Trying to insulate you in that shit.
别记仇
Come on, now.
妈的
Jesus fuck.
-你能拖延点时间吗  -我说了不算
- Can you slow roll this shit? - It's not my call.
我只管在转监文件上签字
All I do is sign off on the transfers,
然后追踪押运的进展
then track deliveries.
跟联邦快递似的
Like, like FedEx.
行吧 一定要把邦尼和其他头目
All right, keep Bunny and all the other leaders
都留在帐篷城
inside Tent City.
好吧 如果他们
All right, if they get fuckin' moved...
在释放前被转移
before they're supposed to be released,
这整个计划就完蛋了
this whole thing is gonna fuckin' fall apart.
你是在求合作还是指挥我
You askin' or tellin'?
拜托 就配合配合我
Come on. Just fuckin' do it.
你以为你在跟谁讲话
Who do you think you're talking to?
在我眼里你可不是市长 麦克
You're not the mayor to me, Mike.
我可不是你的手下
I don't work for you.
要我照顾这些人
I'm supposed to kid glove these guys,
就为了能帮助你所谓的计划是吗
because it helps some "plan" you think you got?
拳王麦克·泰森的名言
有句话说得好
You know the sayin',
"每个人在挨揍之前都有自己的一套计划"
"Everybody got a plan 'til they get punched in the face."
我挨过揍了
Well, I've been punched in the face,
所以我现在自己制定计划
so I'm makin' my own plans, now.
拜托 喂 喂 别这样
Come on! Hey, hey, hey, come on.
我们要是失去邦尼
We lose Bunny...
再失去其他几个头领
...and you lose all the other generals...
那你的监狱就会乱套
you lose the fuckin' prison.
然后整个金斯敦就他妈没救了
And then we lose fuckin' Kingstown.
蛾摩拉为圣经中的罪恶之城
这里又要变成蛾摩拉了
It's fuckin' Gomorrah all over again.
你的孩子将没有安全的地方可去
And there's nowhere safe for your kid to go.
我不是求你帮我
I'm not asking you to fuckin' help me.
这事对我没啥好处
I get nothing outta this.
我是叫你帮助你自己
I'm tellin' you to fuckin' help yourself.
你有这权力 卡里姆 用它
You have the power, Kareem. So use it.
好吧
All right?
当铺 枪和子弹
你好吗 贺拉斯
What's goin' on there, Horace?
嗨 科尔顿
Hey, Colton.
我还以为你和老婆戒了毒了
I thought you and the lady kicked.
我只是...
I just...
我有个问题
I got a question.
我需要帮助 但不知道该问谁
I need some help, and I didn't know who to ask.
你是要当东西吗
Look man, you got somethin' to pawn?
你要是想买点东西或者买毒品 我都有
If you wanna buy some shit or score some shit, I got you.
Dear Abby是专门给读者提供生活建议的报刊专栏
不是的话我可没空当你的知心大姐
Otherwise I ain't got time for your "Dear Abby" shit right now.
我他妈要这玩意有啥用
What the fuck am I supposed to do with this shit?
我手里有价值五万的这些东西
I can give you 50 grand worth of these things.
你要是能出价一万 这买卖就成了
You give me 10 grand, we're solid.
你拿相机录我呢吗
You got me on camera right now?
啥 没有
What? No.
Candid Camera是美国著名整人偷拍节目
我感觉你这跟整人偷拍节目似的
'Cause I figure this gotta be some Candid Camerabullshit.
我查过了 哥们 这些东西可值钱了
I looked it up, man. This shit's worth real money.
哥们 你要是想跟我买东西 没问题
Look man, if you wanna buy some shit, I got you.
不然的话你就赶紧给我滚
Otherwise, get your skinny ass out of my store.
把你这古董银票也拿走
And take your old-timey bank notes with you.
这真的能当钱花 我发誓 就像...
It's as real as cash, man, I swear, like...
旅行支票一样
fuckin' traveler's checks.
那你去旅行吧 带上你老婆 去巴黎玩个开心
Go take a trip, take your girl, go to Paris, have fun.
给我滚出去
Get the fuck outta my store.
我不知该如何把它们转手
I don't know how to move 'em.
我还以为...
I just thought, you know...
你没准认识什么人
I thought you might know someone.
我是认识一个人 但你可不想认识他
There's someone I know, you don't wanna know.
但我要告诉你一个你知道的事实 贺拉斯
But I'm gonna tell you a truth you already know, Horace.
瞎掺和跟这张纸有关的事
Trying to mess around with shit like this paper will
会把你带往一个鬼地方
take you to a bad place.
一个你绝不会想待的地方
A place you don't wanna be at.
所以不如回家生堆火 开个派对 然后把这些玩意都烧掉
So build a fire, have a party. Burn all this shit up.
忘掉你寄托在这堆纸上的希望和幻想吧
Forget the hopes and dreams you placed on that shit.
你听到了吗
You hear me?
你认识的那个人是谁 告诉我吧
Who do you know? Please.
这是什么书
What is that book?
很高兴你对书感兴趣
Like you care.
不 我不是
No, I do.
是关于古罗马奴隶的书
It's about slaves in ancient Rome.
我是对古罗马的奴隶感兴趣
I care about slaves in ancient Rome.
得了吧
Give me a break.
伊恩
Ian!
等我一会 就一会
Give me one second, one second.
丹尼 怎么了
Danny, what's up?
兄弟 有个非常可怕的消息
Man, it's gonna get freakin' hairy.
锚湾正在释放成千上万个犯人
Anchor Bay is dumpin' 'em by the thousands.
你说什么
What are you talkin' about?
所有的监狱都在这么做
All of the prisons are doin' it.
他们把非暴力罪犯放回到街上
They're kickin' the non-violents back out on the streets,
好给帐篷里的罪犯腾地方
and makin' room for the tent dwellers.
就看那些非暴力罪犯会用多久犯下暴力罪行
Let's see how long it takes for the non-violent to get violent.
-好吧 谢谢  -好的
- All right, thank you. - All right.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
听到了
I did.
老天啊
Jesus Christ, it's gonna be
外面要乱成一锅粥了 米利安
a goddamn mess out there, Mariam.
这个孩子也是同样的问题
This kid is part of the problem.
我们上周把他放走
We let him off last week.
然后他怎么做的
And what'd he do?
出去后又犯事 只用了一把手枪
Went out and did it again, only used a goddamn gun.
我想跟他聊聊
I, I, I just wanna talk to him.
行 好吧 会让你跟他聊聊的
Yeah, well, you'll talk to him.
金斯敦少年犯感化中心
只要你喜欢 你可以跟一大群少年犯聊聊
You'll talk to a whole group of them, like you do.
我只想跟马科聊聊
Well, I wanna talk to Marco.
米利安 这可不行
Mariam, it's not gonna work like that.
我托了关系才让你进来的
I pulled strings to get you in here.
而且 他也不会想跟
And besides, this kid's not gonna wanna talk to
他上周抢劫过的女士聊天的 好吗
the lady that he jumped last week, all right?
米利安 我知道这话听着刺耳
Mariam, I know it sounds shitty.
但讲真 我想说
But honestly, I mean,
他甚至都不记得你长什么样了
he's not even gonna remember what you look like.
好吧 没事
Yeah. Okay.
少年犯
消防水带和灭火器 灭火阀
你们好
Hello.
我想或许我们可以聊一聊彼此的情况
I thought maybe we could just talk between ourselves.
有没有谁有话要说
If anybody has anything to say...
没 没有 当然没有
No, no. Of course not.
好吧 我先说吧
Well, I'll go first.
我是米利安·麦克拉斯基
Okay, so... I'm Mariam McLusky.
我在结婚时搬到了金斯敦
I moved to Kingstown when I married,
我丈夫在这里工作
and my husband had a job here.
我们有三个孩子
And we had three sons.
我一直在监狱工作 到现在差不多有50年了
I've been working in prisons, oh, for almost 50 years now.
但我从没在少年犯感化中心工作过
But I've never worked in juvenile before.
所以这是我第一次到这来
So, this is a first.
我的孩子跟你们一样大的时候
When my boys were about your age,
他们的父亲在飞车射击中被击中杀害
their father was shot and killed in a drive-by.
然后就在去年 我的长子
Then, last year, my oldest son...
在抢劫中被枪杀
was shot and killed in a robbery.
我心里其实
And I just sort of...
充斥着一些愤怒
filled up with rage.
我常把这些怒气撒在二儿子身上
I took it out a lot on my middle boy.
但实际上 我是对这个世界
But really, I was just angry...
感到愤怒
with the world.
我在想 你们中会不会有人能...
And I wonder if any of you can...
我爸爸是在我家门口的门廊上
My pop was killed on our front porch
被杀死的 当时我正在写作业
outside of our house while I was doing homework.
-她让你说话了吗  -可以的
- She say talk? - Oh, yes.
我想让他们说话 谢谢
Oh, I want them to talk. Thank you.
他们可以说话 请继续
But they can talk. Please, go on.
我想说的就这么多
That's all I've got to say.
你叫什么
What's your name?
雅各布
Jacob.
有个混蛋就在我妹妹的破学校外把她杀害了
Fuckin' killed my baby sister right outside her goddamn school.
结果就是一堆狗屁事
Caught up in some bullshit.
没有审判 没有抗议 什么都没有
No trial, no protests, no nothin'.
那你又为什么来这呢 我知道你是谁
Why you here, anyway? I know who you are.
也知道你儿子是谁
I know who your son is.
这个
Well...
在上个月那场监狱暴乱里
Last month, in the prison riot,
当监狱里着火的时候
both my boys were trapped inside the prison
我两个儿子都被困在里面
when it was on fire,
我以为再也见不到他们了
and I didn't think that I would ever see them again.
当他们从里面走出来的时候
And when they walked out...
我心里似乎有什么东西裂开了
something inside of me just cracked wide open.
我所有的愤怒
And it's like all the...
仿佛都挥散而出
rage leaked out.
心里只剩下感激之情
And what was left was thankfulness.
然后上周 我被抢劫了
Then last week, I was mugged,
那个男孩打了我一拳 还把我推倒在地
and the boy punched me and he threw me down,
但他没破坏任何东西
but he didn't break anything.
而且
And...
他只拿走了现金
He just took my cash.
他没带走我的照片 钱包和提包
He left me my photos, and my wallet, my bag.
我还不太明白 我猜我依旧感到
And I don't know, I guess I'm just still...
感激
thankful.
不好意思 我想找约瑟夫聊聊
Excuse me. I'm supposed to talk to Joseph.
你是在找死
It's your funeral.
你知道他在哪吗
You know where he is?
你好 我是艾丽丝
Hi. I'm Iris.
你好 艾丽丝
Hello, Iris.
我是迈克尔 叫我麦克吧
I'm Michael, Mike.
所以 这是你最近找到的
So, you just found this?
而且这东西还有不少
And there are more?
是
Yeah...
在我工地里
at my construction site.
东西还在那吗
They are still there?
不 求你了...
No, please...
东西很安全 兄弟 在安全的地方
They're safe, man. They're in a safe place.
在哪个安全的地方
Where is safe?
你想要吗
You want 'em?
那东西肯定价值有百万了
Sure there'd be like, like millions worth.
我可以交给你 只取一点儿报酬
I'll give 'em to ya pennies on the dollar.
我们现在是在谈判吗
We're making deals, now?
喂 怎么了 邦尼
Yeah, what's up, Bunny?
麦克 这里他妈出大事了
Hey, shit is poppin' off over here, Mike.
你必须立马滚到帐篷城来
You need to get your ass down over to the tents.
就现在 狗日的
Now, motherfucker!
好 马上到
Okay. Be right there.
喂 史蒂夫 怎么了
Hey, Stevie. What's up?
麦克 你得来局里一趟
Hey, Mikey. You need to come to the station.
不 我不行
No, I can't.
我...你直接说吧
I... Just tell me.
好 我这儿有些东西你应该想看看 兄弟
Yeah, I got somethin' that you wanna see, man.
我们得在警长听到风声前想出对付策略
We gotta figure out a play before Chief gets wind of it.
好吧 我明天去
All right, I'll come in tomorrow.
麦克 我不是想逼你
Mikey, I'm not tryin' to be pushy.
但你必须来看看
You need to see this.
这不是可以留到明天的事儿
This is somethin' they ain't gonna keep 'til tomorrow.
操 妈的
Fuck. Jesus.
操 史蒂夫 行吧 就五分钟 行吗
Fuck, Steve, fine! Five minutes, all right?
那就够了
That's all I need.
-后门见  -我来了
- Meet me out back. - I'm comin'.
好了 史蒂夫 你发现什么了
All right, Stevie. What have you got?
看
Look.
那女士说她丈夫在工作现场挖出了一箱这样的东西
Lady said her husband dug up a box of these at his work site.
箱子呢
Where is this box?
锁起来了
Lock up.
她把东西都放到一个运动包里了
She threw 'em in a fuckin' gym bag.
我的妈呀
Jesus Christ.
我不能就让东西就那样在外面放着 兄弟
I couldn't just fuckin' leave 'em sittin' out there, man.
她有多少这东西
Well, how many of these does she have?
我不清楚 很多
I don't know. A lot.
大概所有的都在她那儿了
Like, probably fuckin' all of 'em.
操
Fuck.
麦克 我得清楚我们对这事儿要挖多深
Mike, I gotta know how deep we're gonna go here with this.
听着 首先我们不能让这些东西被司法部发现
Look, we gotta keep 'em out of the fuckin' system, first of all.
好吗 给我点时间
Okay? Can you buy me a minute?
我正在这么做
That's what I'm doin'.
还有人知道你有这东西吗
Anybody else know you got these?
刚拿到
Just dropped in.
所以这女士有什么事
So, what's up with this lady?
她根本不在乎这些债券 兄弟
She don't give a shit about the bonds, man.
她只是想保护她丈夫
She's just tryin' to protect her husband.
她丈夫人呢
Where is he?
不清楚 兄弟
Not sure, man.
好吧 听着
Okay, all right, look.
跟她说我们会处理好债券的事情 好吗
Tell her that we're gonna take care of the bonds, okay?
她应该回家等她丈夫
And that she should go home and wait for her husband.
如果他没回来
If he doesn't come back,
她得立马搬家走人 换个地方住
she should find a new fuckin' zip code.
好吗 我得走了
All right? I gotta go.
把这放到你保险箱里或者什么地方
Put these in your fuckin' trunk or somethin'.
麦洛会来找他的东西的
Milo's gonna come lookin' for what's his.
你懂吗
You understand?
别和任何人说这事
Don't talk to anybody about this shit.
那东西是饵 看看我们能钓上什么
This shit's baited! Let's see what we get.
我做了什么啊
What have I done?
哦 不
Oh no!
操
Fuck!
冷静 冷静 没有救生衣值班 不能游泳
Calm down, calm down! No lifeguard on duty, no swim!
你们都别推了 冷静一下
Y'all can stop pushin' and calm your little asses down.
除非有救生员上班 不然谁都不能接近泳池
Nobody gets near that pool 'til there's a lifeguard on duty.
该你上场表演了
Show time.
抱歉 大家 我的错 我的错
Sorry, y'all! My bad, my bad.
车出了问题
Car problems.
听着 在我们开门前
Look, before we open up these gates,
我们得进行一个安全说明
we havin' a safety meetin'.
好吗 不许跑步
All right? No runnin'.
不许在泳池里吃东西
No food in the pool.
我说话的时候你能不能把声音关小点
And you wanna turn that down while I'm talkin'?
谢谢你
Thank you.
好了
All right!
警告一次
I warn you once!
出去15分钟
You're out for 15 minutes.
警告两次
I warn you twice!
出去30分钟
Out for 30.
警告三次 就去给你妈妈打电话
Three times, go ahead and call your mama,
因为你不能继续在这玩了
'cause your day is done here.
都同意吗
We good?
好
Yeah!
来吧 来吧 来吧
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
我说什么了 不许跑
What'd I say? No runnin'!
-他们不会听话 对吧  -对 他们不
- They don't listen, do they? - No, they don't.
-人肉炮弹  -走路 走路 走路
- Cannonball! - Walk, walk, walk!
《金斯敦市长》下集预告
唯一一个会为了这些债券杀人的人
The only person that's gonna kill for these bonds
是要抛售这些债券的人
is the person that can flip them.
你是说麦洛还在外面吗
You're saying Milo's still out there?
我们一起工作吧 麦克
Let's work together, Mike.
让一切回到正轨
Get shit back to the way that it was.
他们把所有的囚犯都转移出帐篷城了
They transferred all the inmates out of Tent City.
邦尼收拾了这堆烂摊子 你记着
Bunny looked after the world. Know that.
你最好把他弄出来
You best get him out,
否则你也会有麻烦的
or the fuzz gonna be comin' your way too.
你难道不觉得如果麦克·麦克拉斯基能解决这事
Don't you think if Mike McLusky could fix this,
他现在应该已经解决了吗
he would've fixed it by now?
当我说我要做一件事的时候 这事绝对会成
When I say I'll do a thing, that thing gets fucking done.